9854 National Blvd., Unit 519, Los Angeles, CA 90034 **4** (310) 272-0457 **4** perrys222242@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Strong problem-solving, detail-orientation and database-querying abilities are balanced by broad exposure to the manufacturing, service and investment industries. A track record of streamlining workflows through macros/automation, boosting data quality through incorporating master data, identifying errors in calculation from auditing, unlocking information by working around flawed data models, has been proven.

EDUCATION:

General Assembly — **Data Science Immersive** USC – MARSHALL SCHOOL OF BUSINESS

Los Angeles, CA

SC – MARSHALL SCHOOL OF BUSINESS Los Angeles, CA

Master of Business Administration – Finance, Management Accounting

National University of Singapore – semester of International Business

UCLA-EXTENSION – Oracle PL/SQL

Los Angeles, CA

University of California, at Davis

Davis, CA

Master of Science

University of Western Ontario

Honors Bachelor of Science

London, Ontario, Canada

PROJECTS:

Credit-card Default Risk

- Supervised binary classification using neural-networks, decision-trees modeling Sub-Reddit Post-Title
- Supervised binary classification using web-scraping, NLP, logistic regression modeling Ames-housing Price Prediction
- Supervised multivariate linear regression with regularization, for Kaggle competition

EXPERIENCE:

2018 CITY NATIONAL BANK/Data Office

Los Angeles, CA

- Led data-quality assessments of critical-data elements for lines of business and enterprise repositories
- Environment: Office, Tableau, Visio, T-SQL, TOAD

2016-2017 AMGEN/Master-Data Analyst

Thousand Oaks, CA

TECHSTYLE/Workday Project Coordinator

El Segundo, CA

- Scrubbed and reconstructed Supplier-Master data for Source-to-pay project, adding accountgroup structure
- Coordinated Workday implementation, created HCM/Benefits workbooks for integration team; drove payroll integration with ADP using macros, loading EIB's, including testing and troubleshooting
- Environment: MS-PowerPoint, Ariba, DataStewardProfiler, Outlook, VBA, SAP S4-HANA, Workday

2015 HONDA MOTOR/Data Analyst

Los Angeles, CA

ZODIAC-DRIESSEN/Data Analyst

Anaheim, CA

CAST&CREW/Senior Analyst

Burbank, CA

- Tracked and automated periodic-access reviews for OS and database roles and user/service accounts
- Reporting metrics with automated chart updates for 787 product-development project

PERRY SHYR, MBA

- Building and upgrading Excel-VBA tools/calculators to enhance productivity through automated e-mail and presentation creation, based on extensive requirements gathering; automated a manual 3-day report into a 3-minute macro with downward compatibility
- Environment: MS-PowerPoint, MS Project, CATIA, SmarTeam, Notes, SharePoint, VBA

2013-2014 DISNEY-ABC TV/MDM/Data Steward

Burbank, CA

Burbank, CA

- NORTH HIGHLAND/Master-data Consultant
- Conceptualized Master-data Management (MDM) workflow for Shared Data Repository (SDR)
 Proposed enhancements/workarounds to data-visualization applications in Production from requirements gathered; audited and scrubbed RPD with 20-million Facts added daily
- Constructed 50,000 record master-table from five-plus disparate internal sources and formats
- Environment: Endeca, Informatica, JIRA, SAP, Confluence, NielsenSocialGuide, SAS, Hadoop, Aginity/Neteeza

2012 RAPISCAN SYSTEMS/QA Analyst VANS/Data Analyst

Torrance, CA

Cypress, CA

ONE WEST BANK/Analyst-IV

Pasadena, CA

- Recovered a complete list of regional installations in Latin America leading to \$1.29m+, in new contracts/sales
- Loaded, tested and maintained B2B-data for seasonal product lines in separate markets on web-application
- Project coordinator for Consent-Order administration of foreclosure-complaint reviews by 3rd-party; daily, weekly & monthly reporting, UAT, data-integrity, process management, statistical analysis
- Environment: Dynamics-NAV, WebSphere-Commerce, SharePoint, CATSweb, MS Access/Powerpoint, Visio

2009-2011 LFP BROADCASTING/Senior Data Analyst

Los Angeles, CA

- Prepared monthly reports for revenue-sharing, royalties and daily-cash balances for upper management
- Proposed and implemented new scalable processes and workflows to boost productivity
- Found over \$670,000 in calculation errors covering payments dating back to 2006
- Environment: Intuitive 8.1, MS Access-2007, MirC, Excel-VBA, SS Mgmt-Studio-2008

2008 TOYOTA FINANCIAL SERVICES/Consultant

Torrance, CA

- Proposed software enhancement to save roughly \$230,000 annually including \$34,000 in wasted postage; discovered at least 125,000 new name data-truncation errors
- Environment: Siebel, SQL-Server RS, Tibco, Focus, Trillium, Excel-VBA, Notes, FastData, DMS, Rumba

2007 KAISER PERMANENTE/Consultant

Pasadena, CA

2006 ARES MANAGEMENT/Consultant

Century City, CA

NBC-UNIVERSAL/Consultant

Universal City, CA

• Environment: Portia, Bloomberg, Office, BO, Excel, Notes, Crystal Reports, Hyperion, SAP

SKILLS: Con

2005

Computer literacy in SAP, Siebel, Portia, VBA for Office, Oracle, SharePoint, Websphere, Dynamics, CATSweb, Informatica. Conversational speaking and writing in French; some Chinese fluency.